Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3
- Box: 64, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 64, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Woman's work, 1972; Publication (Box 64, Folder 70)
    Author: Working Women's Association, Vancouver, B.C., B.C.
- Box: 64, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 64, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: A revolution in production in China, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 71)
- Box: 64, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 64, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Develop labour emulation in honour of the 30th anniversary of the Communist Party of China., 1951; Publication (Box 64, Folder 72)
    Author: Li Lisan
- Box: 64, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 64, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Militant railway workers of China, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 73)
    Author: Zhonghua quan guo zong gong hui
- Box: 64, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 64, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The general condition of the textile workers' union of China, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 74)
    Author: Preparatory committee of Textile Workers' Union of China
- Box: 64, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 64, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Trade union law of the People's Republic of China, 1950; Publication (Box 64, Folder 75)
- Box: 64, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 64, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Appeal and resolutions, 1982; Publication (Box 64, Folder 76)
    Author: World Trade Union Congress
- Box: 64, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 64, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Czechoslovakia's cooperative movement following the 6th Congress of the Central Cooperative Council, 1971; Publication (Box 64, Folder 77)
    Author: Mikulas Capek
- Box: 64, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 64, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Trade unions and employed women in Czechoslovakia, 1967; Publication (Box 64, Folder 78)
    Author: Jirina Brejchova
- Box: 64, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 64, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: A.B.C. du syndicalisme, 1927; Publication (Box 64, Folder 79)
    Author: Firmin Bacconnier
- Box: 64, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 64, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Bilan des operations, Publication (Box 64, Folder 80)
    Author: La Concorde. Societe cooperative des ouvriers du bassin de Charleroi
- Box: 64, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 64, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Caisse des retraites pour la vieillesse, 1861; Publication (Box 64, Folder 81)
    Author: A.Vitard
- Box: 64, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 64, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Catholique et syndicaliste, 1908; Publication (Box 64, Folder 82)
    Author: Andre Vral
- Box: 64, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 64, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Causerie sur la mutualite, 1908; Publication (Box 64, Folder 83)
    Author: Felix de Pachtere
- Box: 64, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 64, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Ce qu'il faut savoir sur les assurances sociales, 1937; Publication (Box 64, Folder 84)
    Author: Miniconi
- Box: 64, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 64, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Connaissez-vous la cooperation?, 1937; Publication (Box 64, Folder 85)
    Author: Gaston Prache
- Box: 64, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 64, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Des limitations naturelles aux lois ouvrie`res internationales, 1890; Publication (Box 64, Folder 86)
    Author: Armand Julin
- Box: 64, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 64, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Des societes cooperatives de consommation, 1866; Publication (Box 64, Folder 87)
    Author: Jules Duval
- Box: 64, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 64, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Du progre`s industriel et agricole, 1863; Publication (Box 64, Folder 88)
    Author: J.B. Lambert
- Box: 64, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 64, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Esprit revolutionnaire et syndicalisme, 1914; Publication (Box 64, Folder 89)
    Author: J. Mesnil
- Box: 64, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 64, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Estatutos de la Asociacion Internacional de los Trabajadores, 1958; Publication (Box 64, Folder 90)
    Author: International Working Men's Association
- Box: 64, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 64, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Est-ce que le batiment va?, 1957; Publication (Box 64, Folder 91)
    Author: Pierre Dichamps
- Box: 64, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 64, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Gre`ve heroique des 120,000 mineurs du Nord et du Pas-de-Calais, du 26 mai au 10 juin 1941, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 92)
    Author: Roger Collewaert
- Box: 64, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 64, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Jules Guesde et les gre`ves, 1949; Publication (Box 64, Folder 93)
    Author: Jules Guesde
- Box: 64, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 64, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: La dotation syndicale, 1920; Publication (Box 64, Folder 94)
    Author: Rene Favareille
- Box: 64, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 64, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: La conference officielle de Berne (Mai 1905), Publication (Box 64, Folder 95)
    Author: Conference officielle de Berne
- Box: 64, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 64, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: La federation syndicale internationale, 1937; Publication (Box 64, Folder 96)
    Author: Georges Stolz
- Box: 64, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 64, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: La gre`ve generale et la revolution, 1899; Publication (Box 64, Folder 97)
    Author: Aristide Briand
- Box: 64, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 64, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: La paix des classes, 1918; Publication (Box 64, Folder 98)
    Author: J. Albessard
- Box: 64, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 64, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: La primaute du travail, 1941; Publication (Box 64, Folder 99)
    Author: Aime Rey
- Box: 64, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 64, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: La reforme economique et sociale, 1918; Publication (Box 64, Folder 100)
    Author: George Valois
- Box: 64, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 64, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: La rele`ve, 1943; Publication (Box 64, Folder 101)
    Author: Denise V. Ayme
- Box: 64, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 64, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: La sedition ouvrie`re de 1786, 1907; Publication (Box 64, Folder 102)
    Author: J. Beyssac
- Box: 64, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 64, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: La semaine de 40 heures et la reduction du temps de travail, 1937; Publication (Box 64, Folder 103)
    Author: Rene Belin
- Box: 64, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 64, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: La situation du placement dans la region du nord, 1912; Publication (Box 64, Folder 104)
    Author: Alfred Dodanthun
- Box: 65, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: L'avenir de la C.G.T., 1939; Publication (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Author: Michel Fontgrave
- Box: 65, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Le capitalisme contemporain, 1937; Publication (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Author: Rene Bouyer
- Box: 65, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Le code du travail et l'hygie`ne, 1937; Publication (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Author: Guy Hausser
- Box: 65, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Le droit de gre`ve, 1937; Publication (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Author: Albert Guigui
- Box: 65, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Le plan de la C.G.T., Publication (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Author: Ludovic Zoretti
- Box: 65, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Le proble`me de la main-d'oevre etrange`re, 1938; Publication (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Box: 65, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Le salaire ..., 1905; Publication (Box 65, Folder 7)
    Author: L. Garriguet
- Box: 65, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Le syndicalisme chretien en 1945, Publication (Box 65, Folder 8)
    Author: Gaston Tessier
- Box: 65, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Le travail des enfants, 1907; Publication (Box 65, Folder 9)
    Author: Paul Gemahling
- Box: 65, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Le Veritable syndicalisme, 1969; Publication (Box 65, Folder 10)
- Box: 65, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: L'Eglise et les travailleurs, Publication (Box 65, Folder 11)
    Author: P. Croizier
- Box: 65, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Les anciens combattants et la Confederation generale du travail, 1934; Publication (Box 65, Folder 12)
- Box: 65, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Les aspects sociaux du mouvement cooperatif belge, conference prononcee a` Paris, 1e 29 mars 1951, Publication (Box 65, Folder 13)
    Author: Julien Papart
- Box: 65, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Les cho^meurs d'apre`s une enque^te recente, 1942; Publication (Box 65, Folder 14)
    Author: Charles Rist
- Box: 65, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Les classes laborieuses sous l'ancien regime, Publication (Box 65, Folder 15)
    Author: Emile Dantinne
- Box: 65, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Les conges payes, 1937; Publication (Box 65, Folder 16)
    Author: Albert Gazier
- Box: 65, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Les conges payes, 1948; Publication (Box 65, Folder 17)
    Author: CGT-FO (Union)
- Box: 65, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Les Societes cooperatives de production, 1867; Publication (Box 65, Folder 18)
- Box: 65, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Les syndicats professionnels, 1883; Publication (Box 65, Folder 19)
    Author: Albert Mun
- Box: 65, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Livret de travail des enfants ages de moins de 18 ans occupes dans les etablissements industriels et commerciaux, 1938; Publication (Box 65, Folder 20)
    Author: France. Ministere du travail
- Box: 65, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: L'Organisation internationale du travail, 1923; Publication (Box 65, Folder 21)
    Author: Paul Devinat
- Box: 65, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: L'U.R.S.S. ses victoires socialistes, 1936; Publication (Box 65, Folder 22)
    Author: Pierre Semard
- Box: 65, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: L'unite syndical, Publication (Box 65, Folder 23)
    Author: Cercle d'Etudes et d'Action Syndicale; Confederation generale du travail
- Box: 65, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: L'unite syndicale internationale, la paix, la renaissance economique de la France, 1945; Publication (Box 65, Folder 24)
    Author: Benoit Frachon
- Box: 65, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Manifeste de l'Alliance syndicaliste, Publication (Box 65, Folder 25)
    Author: Alliance syndicaliste (France)
- Box: 65, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Napoleon III et sa bonte, 1910; Publication (Box 65, Folder 26)
    Author: Pauline Bletry
- Box: 65, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Organisation de la marche des operations dans une usine ne travaillant pas en serie, 1929; Publication (Box 65, Folder 27)
    Author: J. Louis
- Box: 65, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Les ouvriers, les syndicats & les anarchistes, Publication (Box 65, Folder 28)
    Author: E. Armand
- Box: 65, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Paix sociale et internationale, 1911; Publication (Box 65, Folder 29)
    Author: Emile Lewy
- Box: 65, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Petit manuel d'education syndicale, 1919; Publication (Box 65, Folder 30)
    Author: Action populaire (Institute: France)
- Box: 65, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Pour l'apprentissage, 1909; Publication (Box 65, Folder 31)
    Author: A. Boudra
- Box: 65, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Question sociale, 1895; Publication (Box 65, Folder 32)
    Author: E. Matignon
- Box: 65, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Reflexions sur une definition de l'artisan, 1942; Publication (Box 65, Folder 33)
    Author: Gabriel Daty
- Box: 65, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Statuts modifies au Congre`s de Toulouse 1929, Publication (Box 65, Folder 34)
    Author: Federation francaise des travailleurs du livre
- Box: 65, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Syndicalisme et politique, Publication (Box 65, Folder 35)
    Author: Jacques C. Perier
- Box: 65, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Syndicats d'officiers, 1911; Publication (Box 65, Folder 36)
    Author: Robert de Boisfleury
- Box: 65, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Testament d'un ouvrier, 1883; Publication (Box 65, Folder 37)
- Box: 65, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The truth about the French Miners' Strike, 1948; Publication (Box 65, Folder 38)
- Box: 65, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Un mois en Russie cooperative, 1922; Publication (Box 65, Folder 39)
    Author: E. Poisson
- Box: 65, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Une attitude, un programme, 1927; Publication (Box 65, Folder 40)
    Author: Confederation generale du travail
- Box: 65, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Voeux proposes renseignements divers, 1894; Publication (Box 65, Folder 41)
    Author: Congres oubrier chretien
- Box: 65, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: XIXme Congre`s de l'Office Cooperatif Belge, (A.S.B.L.), a` Seraing, les 18, 19 et 20 Juin 1932: rapport general annuel, Publication (Box 65, Folder 42)
    Author: Office Cooperatif Belge. Congre`s
- Box: 65, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Arbeiter und Weltwirtschaft, 1930; Publication (Box 65, Folder 43)
    Author: Wilhelm Eggert
- Box: 65, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Aus der Praxis der Betriebsrate, 1946; Publication (Box 65, Folder 44)
- Box: 65, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Bericht der Sozialisierungskommission uber die Frage der Sozialisierung des Kohlenbergbaues vom 31. Juli 1920, 1921; Publication (Box 65, Folder 45)
    Author: Germany. Sozialisierungskommission
- Box: 65, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Argumente zur Sozialisierung, 1947; Publication (Box 65, Folder 46)
    Author: Gewerkschaftliches Zonensekretariat (Britische Zone)
  - Item 2: Betriebsrate und Vertrauensleute, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 46)
    Author: Industriegewerkschaft Metall fur die Bundesrepublik Deutschland.
- Box: 65, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 65, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Das Betriebsrategesetz, 1946; Publication (Box 65, Folder 47)
- Box: 65, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 65, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Das neue Recht im Betriebsratewesen, 1948; Publication (Box 65, Folder 48)
- Box: 65, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 65, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Der deutsche Kohlenbergbau und die Energiewirtschaft, Publication (Box 65, Folder 49)
    Author: Industriegewerkschaft Bergbau und Energie
- Box: 65, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 65, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Der Tarifvertrag und Du, Publication (Box 65, Folder 50)
    Author: Erich Weber
- Box: 65, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 65, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Der Werksarzt in der modernen industriellen Arbeitswelt, Publication (Box 65, Folder 51)
    Author: Werner Matzies
- Box: 65, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 65, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Die Arbeitslosenversicherung einschliesslich Kurzarbeiterunterstutzung, sowie Arbeitslosenfursorgeunterstutzung, 1950; Publication (Box 65, Folder 52)
    Author: Walter Henkelmann
- Box: 65, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 65, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Die Menschenrechte, 1951; Publication (Box 65, Folder 53)
    Author: Institut zur Forderung 0ffentlicher Angelegenheiten; Deutscher Bund fur Burgerrechte; Germany (West). Deutsche UNESCO-Kommission
- Box: 65, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 65, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Die Neuordnung in der Montanwirtschaft und die Mitbestimmung in den Holding-Gesellschaften, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 54)
    Author: Heinrich Deist
- Box: 65, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 65, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Die wirtschaftliche und gesellschaftliche Lage des jugendlichen Arbeiters in Industrie und Handwerk, 1931; Publication (Box 65, Folder 55)
    Author: Albert Flygare
- Box: 65, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 65, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Jugendarbeitsschutz: Aufgabe und Gestaltung, Publication (Box 65, Folder 56)
    Author: Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund. Landesbezirk Nordrhein-Westfalen
- Box: 65, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 65, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Marx contra Stalin, 1934; Publication (Box 65, Folder 57)
    Author: Ernst Bose
- Box: 65, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 65, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Probleme und Zielsetzungen der Gemeinwirtschaft, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 58)
    Author: Max Brauer
- Box: 65, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 65, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Richtig fuhren, 1941; Publication (Box 65, Folder 59)
    Author: Paul Michligk
- Box: 65, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 65, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Staat und gewerkschaftliche Aktion, Publication (Box 65, Folder 60)
    Author: Alfred Weber
- Box: 65, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 65, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Tag um Tag, Publication (Box 65, Folder 61)
    Author: Georg Busing
- Box: 65, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 65, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: The trade unions in a socialist state, 1963; Publication (Box 65, Folder 62)
    Author: Rudolf Hengmith
- Box: 65, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 65, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Vortrage gehalten auf der Konferenz von Vertrauensleuten am 3. und 4. Marz 1952 in Frankfurt am Main, Publication (Box 65, Folder 63)
- Box: 65, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 65, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Warum Mitbestimmung in der Wirtschaft, 1949; Publication (Box 65, Folder 64)
    Author: Karl Hinkel
- Box: 65, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 65, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Werden und wachsen der neuen Gewerkschaftsbewegung: Ausstellung, Hannover, 7.-9. 9. 1949, Publication (Box 65, Folder 65)
    Author: Deutscher Gewerkschaftsbund (Britische Zone)
- Box: 65, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 65, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: S.I.R. strike, for security of service in defence of their Union, 1946; Publication (Box 65, Folder 66)
    Author: N.K. Krishnan
- Box: 65, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 65, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: A socio-economic survey of jute labour, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 67)
    Author: K.P. Chattopadhyay
- Box: 65, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 65, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: The axe to the root, 1921; Publication (Box 65, Folder 68)
    Author: James Connolly
- Box: 65, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 65, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Irish workers' road to freedom, 1949; Publication (Box 65, Folder 69)
    Author: Irish Workers' League
- Box: 65, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 65, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Brevi note illustrative della Carta del lavoro, 1929; Publication (Box 65, Folder 70)
- Box: 65, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 65, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Fascism: a conquest of the proletariat, 1938; Publication (Box 65, Folder 71)
- Box: 65, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 65, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: La vita di Giuseppe di Vittorio, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 72)
    Author: Felice Chilanti
- Box: 65, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 65, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Metodi e discipline della cooperazione, 1923; Publication (Box 65, Folder 73)
    Author: Silvio Galli
- Box: 65, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 65, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: The syndical reform and the Ministry of the Corporations, 1927; Publication (Box 65, Folder 74)
- Box: 65, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 65, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Unions versus menegement [sic], 1971; Publication (Box 65, Folder 75)
    Author: Joseph Edwards
- Box: 65, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 65, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: For genuine "minimum wage law" of Japan, 1959; Publication (Box 65, Folder 76)
    Author: Nihon rodo Kumiai Sohyogikai
- Box: 65, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 65, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: El movimiento rielero, 1965; Publication (Box 65, Folder 77)
    Author: Comite Nacional de Lucha Obrera Ferroviaria (Mexico)
- Box: 65, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 65, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: La C.T.M. y la carestia de la vida., 1937; Publication (Box 65, Folder 78)
- Box: 65, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 65, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: De kleermakers en hun strijd voor goede arbeidsvoorwaarden, Publication (Box 65, Folder 79)
    Author: T. van der Heeg
- Box: 65, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 65, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: De vrijheid in boeien, Publication (Box 65, Folder 80)
    Author: P.J. Molendijk
- Box: 65, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 65, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: On the present conditions of the labour movement in Japan, 1953; Publication (Box 65, Folder 81)
    Author: Nihon Keieisha Dantai Renmei
- Box: 65, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 65, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Op weg naar het Staatspensioen, 1928; Publication (Box 65, Folder 82)
    Author: G.W. Sannes
- Box: 65, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 65, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Wachter, wat is er van de nacht?, Publication (Box 65, Folder 83)
    Author: Centrale Nederlandse Ambtenaarsbond
- Box: 65, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 65, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Consumers' co-operation in Norway, 1972; Publication (Box 65, Folder 84)
    Author: Liv Ovesen
- Box: 65, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 65, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Raadssystemet og socialiseringen, 1920; Publication (Box 65, Folder 85)
    Author: Alfred Madsen
- Box: 65, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 65, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Trade unions in People's Poland, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 86)
- Box: 65, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 65, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Industrial relations and race relations, 1952; Publication (Box 65, Folder 87)
    Author: Guy Routh
- Box: 65, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 65, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Job reservation and the trade unions, 1959; Publication (Box 65, Folder 88)
    Author: R.E. Simons
- Box: 65, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 65, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Poverty wages: an examination of wage policy in relation to South Africa's lowest paid workers, 1959; Publication (Box 65, Folder 89)
    Author: Alexander Hepple
- Box: 65, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 65, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Spanish trade unions' experience, 1954; Publication (Box 65, Folder 90)
    Author: Jose Solis Ruiz
- Box: 65, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 65, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Employees' provident fund, 1997; Publication (Box 65, Folder 91)
- Box: 65, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 65, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Cog or collaborator, 1946; Publication (Box 65, Folder 92)
    Author: Herman Stolpe
- Box: 65, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 65, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Effective price control, 1944; Publication (Box 65, Folder 93)
    Author: Kooperativa forbundet
- Box: 65, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 65, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Bilder aus dem genossenschaftlichen Tier- und Pflanzenleben, Publication (Box 65, Folder 94)
    Author: Henry Faucherre
- Box: 65, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 65, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Die Genossenschaftsidee und die heutige Wirtschaft, 1936; Publication (Box 65, Folder 95)
    Author: Bernhard Jaeggi
- Box: 65, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 65, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: L'organisation internationale du travail, 1928; Publication (Box 65, Folder 96)
    Author: M. Harmel
- Box: 65, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 65, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: The International non-manual workers' movement, 1938; Publication (Box 65, Folder 97)
    Author: International Federation of Commercial, Clerical, and Technical Employees
- Box: 66, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Hope for the worker, 1913; Publication (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Author: L.G. Chiozza Money
- Box: 66, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Hours and wages boards in the cooperative movement, 1932; Publication (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Author: Frank Jones
- Box: 66, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: How can we avoid the tragedy of back to the dole, 1952; Publication (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Author: Barbara Castle
- Box: 66, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 66, Folder 4)